<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Martin Thorne\'s CV</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_open">Open navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_close">Close navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="speed_dial_email">Email</string>
    <string name="speed_dial_linkedin">LinkedIn</string>
    <string name="speed_dial_github">GitHub</string>
    <string name="settings_menu">Settings</string>
    <string name="settings_popup_increase_text_size">Increase text size</string>
    <string name="settings_popup_decrease_text_size">Decrease text size</string>
    <string name="complete_title">Complete CV</string>

    <string name="main_title">Home</string>
    <string name="main_text"><![CDATA[This app was created to show potential employees my abilities in coding Android applications.<br>
        It was created using <a href="https://developer.android.com/studio">Android Studio.</a> <br> <br>
        Navigate between sections by swiping left or right or using the navigation drawer.]]></string>

    <string name="about_me_title">About Me</string>
    <string name="about_me_text"><![CDATA[Self motivated and hard working individual looking to change careers.<br>
       Having achieved a 2.1 honours degree in information technology and computing, along with other qualifications, whilst working full time helped me improve qualities such as time management, dedication, ambition and commitment.<br>
       Recently made redundant, due to falling orders, my job was as a quality auditor for Sanoh UK, a parts supplier for the automotive industry. Since then I have continued to study, via free online courses, and create apps for Android.<br>
       I am looking to work in the areas of computing and IT. My main area of expertise is programming. This was the most challenging and enjoyable aspect of my studies.<br>]]></string>

    <string name="education_title">Education</string>
    <string name="education_text"><![CDATA[<b>OpenLearn (2019):</b><br>
        This offshoot of the Open University has a large selection of free courses.<br><br>
        Courses completed:<br>
        Everyday Maths: Succeed With Maths Part 1: Succeed With Maths Part 2: Introduction to Computational Thinking: Modelling object-oriented software: Representing and manipulating data in computers<br>
        My OpenLearn profile can be found <a href="https://www.open.edu/openlearn/profiles/mjt272/achievements">here.</a><br><br>

        <b>Udacity (2019):</b><br>
        ‘Android Basics’ nano-degree courses completed:<br>
        User Interface: User Input: Multiscreen Apps: Networking<br><br>

        <b>Open University:</b><br>
        2012: Bachelor of Science (Honours) in Information Technology and Computing (2.1)<br>
        2009: Diploma in Computing<br>
        2008: Certificate in Computing and Mathematics<br>
        2006: Certificate in Information Technology and Computing<br><br>
        Courses completed:<br>
        The Computing And IT Project: Fundamentals Of Interaction Design: Keeping Ahead In Information And Communication Technologies: Software Engineering With Objects: Communication And Information Technologies: Computer And Processors: Designing Applications With Visual Basic: Software Development With Java: Open Mathematics: Putting Computer Systems To Work: Object-Orientated Programming With Java: Data, Computing And The Net: You, Your Computer And The Net<br><br>
        Skills acquired through study:
        <li>Experience with programming languages: Java, Visual Basic and C++.</li>
        <li>Use of different IDE's: Visual Basic 2008 Express Edition, BlueJ, Eclipse and Netbeans.</li>
        <li>How to use different aspects of Object Orientation: Analysis and specification, design, programming, testing and maintenance.</li>
        <li>An understanding of how computing and network systems work.</li>]]>
    </string>

    <string name="employment_title">Employment</string>
    <string name="employment_text"><![CDATA[<b>Sanoh UK Manufacturing Ltd</b><br>
        Quality Auditor (August 2008 – March 2019)<br>
        Sanoh produces brake and fuel pipes for the automotive industry. As a quality auditor (and as part of the quality team) it was my responsibility to ensure that the companies quality procedures were being maintained and carried out properly.<br><br>
        Skills acquired through work:
        <li>Working within the quality department has given me a keen eye for detail.</li>
        <li>Take precise measurements, using various tools, to ensure parts are within 	customer specifications.</li>
        <li>Be a good communicator and be approachable.</li>
        <li>To work independently using initiative, along with problem solving skills, when investigating potential quality issues.</li>
        <li>Work effectively as part of the quality team.</li>]]>
    </string>

    <string name="android_apps_title">Android Apps</string>
    <string name="android_apps_text"><![CDATA[<b>CV App:</b><br>
        This is a mobile version of my CV. It is broken down into sections that the user can get to by either, swiping between screens, or using the navigation drawer. A settings popup menu allows the user to increase or decrease the text size. There is also a FAB button that, when tapped, brings up a speed dial with links to GitHub, LinkedIn and my email.<br>
        <a href="https://play.google.com/store/apps/details?id=com.martint.androidcv">Google Play</a>/<a href="https://github.com/Martin-Thorne/AndroidCV">GitHub</a><br><br>

        <b>Earthquake App:</b><br>
        Uses Google maps to show recent earthquakes. The earthquake data is obtained via the United States Geological Survey website. The app parses the JSON data adding markers to the map. Tapping a marker will bring up further info on the earthquake via a window. When this is tapped the webpage for the earthquake is displayed via the users default browser.<br>
        <a href="https://play.google.com/store/apps/details?id=com.martint.earthquakeapp">Google Play</a>/<a href="https://github.com/Martin-Thorne/EarthquakeApp ">GitHub</a><br><br>

        <b>The Computing and IT Project:</b><br>
        My final year of studying with the OU included the Computing And IT Project. The study area was largely left up to the student. I chose to write apps for Android using Java.<br>
        The basic idea was to build two apps. These would test the idea that personal navigation could be done via a phones vibration function.<br>
        Programming these apps involved a lot of research into programming for Android. The second app also used Google maps.<br>
        As well as programming, the final report also contained use cases, state machine diagram, activity diagram, code beautification and descriptions of how the code was created via prototyping (Scope/Design, Notes on the programming, Testing).<br>
        The final report can be found <a href="https://drive.google.com/file/d/1LXAl3YT4rAMCeP-iXE-Y3pCHz4RDogFc/view?usp=sharing">here.</a><br>
        Both apps are on <a href="https://github.com/Martin-Thorne/OU_Android_Naviagation_Project ">GitHub</a>. Also a readme file that goes into more detail on both apps.<br>]]>
    </string>

    <string name="interests_title">Interests</string>
    <string name="interests_text"><![CDATA[One of my main interests is in technology and gadgets. Keeping up to date with the world of technology is a passion.<br>
     I also enjoy dancing, specifically Le Roc (French jive). I have previously taught and still enjoy going to dances and classes.]]>
    </string>

    <string-array name="complete">
        <item>@string/about_me_title</item>
        <item>@string/about_me_text</item>
        <item>@string/education_title</item>
        <item>@string/education_text</item>
        <item>@string/employment_title</item>
        <item>@string/employment_text</item>
        <item>@string/android_apps_title</item>
        <item>@string/android_apps_text</item>
        <item>@string/interests_title</item>
        <item>@string/interests_text</item>
    </string-array>

</resources>